I did grow up Mormon there's a lot of
rules when you grow up Mormon as you
know there's no drinking no smoking no
premarital anything and of course the
most logical rule I learned later no
coffee it I know it makes sense now my
friends that didn't grow up Mormon
explain to me no Ben it makes sense you
couldn't drink you couldn't smoke no
premarital anything why stay
awake I we don't even know why you get
out of bed we don't get it
just stay
down it's just going to get
worse it was pretty strict no swearing
either no swearing no swearing although
my mom would spell the swear words cuz
then they don't
count apparently she didn't spell bad
word she didn't spell like a sailor
but she but I understand spelling in
front of you know little kids but
there'd be a whole room full of adult
readers and she was still o d m at h e
double
toothpicks mom we know we can read we
can all read all of us so can God we're
pretty sure he's literate we think he's
highly
literate like she thought she found a
loophole for swearing she spells it
God's up there whoa what' she say did
any did anybody get that did you get
that was that some sort of a code
language was that
Navajo that was Navajo Gabriel fetch me
wind
talker no
swearing my dad would almost swear he'
come close his favorite
shoot I said shoot no you said
shoot which is Texan for shoot
dad and we couldn't we couldn't spell
swear words even if we even spelled a
swear word my mom would knuckle us did
anybody else get knuckled she would
write here once your skull congealed it
was fair game for this middle knuckle
right there to whack that knuckle which
eventually was
arthritic it's seriously call it
rheumatoid arthritis I call it karma
but knuckle you my dad did not knuckle
my dad never knuckle my dad is a
psychiatrist so he did not believe in
hitting to modify Behavior instead he
would sit down uh and adjust our
medication why spank the butt when you
can chemically spank the
brain aren't bad kids you just need
bigger
pills